http://www.2020.ie/page/privacy/7556e9a978127f1f4cb81ef3dd00b7f9

Memory Configurator
Text to help user to use the control, the text for this area can be changed in snippets the snippet to change is MemoryConfiguratorDialogHelp.
You can enter part of a word to search by e.g. Pro will find Proliant,
Opt will find Optiplex
Search for
?
Apple
Aqcess Tech.
Eiger Labs
EliteGroup (ECS)
Iwill
J2 (BlueStar)
VideoChip
Videochip Tech.
Product Search
Please use the form below for a more detailed search. You can search by keywords, price range and arrange the sort results in different orders, depending on your preferences.
If you have trouble locating search results try not using plurals or limit the number of keywords you enter.
Search For:
?
Search
2020 ltd.
Special Offers
New Products
Hot Products
Best Sellers
Product Offers
Contact Us
Facebook
Twitter
Linkedin
Register
Forgotten Password
Login
loading
Leading Irish distribution since 1991
Call (01) 2957708(B2B)
Cables
Cat 5
.5 Metre
1 Metre
2 Metre
3 Metre
5 Metre
8 Metre
Privacy Policy
At 2020 Ltd, we value our relationship with our customers and visitors to our Website, and we are committed to responsible information handling practices. We take our customers' privacy seriously, and want you to feel at ease whenever you visit our Website, access our online services, or participate in our online offerings. Although the various sections of our Website feature different products and services, they all share the online privacy policy outlined below. For more detailed information on how we handle online data, see the specific privacy statements under the links below:
2020 Ltd privacy principles
Our approach to responsible information handling is founded on the Fair Information Practices. In line with these, we have a policy of openness about our information practices and other privacy issues, allowing individuals to make informed decisions regarding personally identifiable information. When you visit our Website, we may ask you to provide data that allows you to participate more fully in our online offerings and services. Whenever we collect personal information, we let you know what is being collected, how it is collected, for what purpose(s) it is collected, and to whom it may be disclosed. We also indicate when information is necessary to provide you with the specific service you require. Whenever we request information that is not required and entirely voluntary, we make this clear so that you know it is not needed to provide the requested service.
Use of cookies
To ensure that the content of our Website is tailored to our customers' requirements, 2020.ie collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track individuals' use of the site. When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on their machine (if it is set to accept cookies) or is read if they have previously visited the site. Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, assist in delivering the cookie. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a 2020.ie Web page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information on Willtek.com; we use this tool only to compile aggregated statistics about Willtek.com Web site usage. We do not share tracking information outside 2020 Ltd, and do not allow other companies to place clear gifs on our sites.
Information about yourself
You may browse our Website without disclosing personal information. However, if you want to receive our online products and services, or participate in other online activities (e.g., surveys and contests), we may ask you to provide us with information about yourself. This information is optional and is not required to visit our sites. When you provide us with personally identifiable information that may be used for secondary purposes (i.e., uses not related to the purpose for which the information was collected), we always give you the opportunity to opt-out of such uses.
Information updates
We have a variety of mechanisms that allow you to modify and update the contact information you have given us, and are currently developing more options for updating personal data. The privacy statements on our Website keep you informed of the options available for modifying the contact information you have provided.
Protect personal information
We operate this Website in line with recognised industry standards and deploy security mechanisms to protect personally identifiable information against unauthorised access and misuse. Furthermore, we take the appropriate measures to ensure that the information used to process your request is accurate and up-to-date.
Changes to this Statement
2020.ie will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. 2020.ie will draw your attention to any material changes to this statement by means of a prominent message on the Website.
Related Documents
About Us
Privacy Policy
RMA Form
Terms & Conditions
WEEE Compliance
Contact Us
Terms And Conditions
2020 ltd.
2020 ltd.
